



(202) 681-8640 Baltimore, MD 21211

## Summary

Professionally, I've enjoyed six years working with at-scale digital publishing brands. Currently, I work on contracts and freelance projects. At my various professional roles I've worked as either a designer, a frontend or a mix of the two. Having a background covering fine arts, print design, plus years pursuing optimal frontend methods while happily stumbling through rails apps has given me an interestingly rounded skill set, spanning visual design and front end development.

## **Employment**

FREELANCE Baltimore, MD Visual & Front End Dev 2013-present

The bulk of my freelance work has been responsive frontend development. In addition, I'm frequently responsible for visual design as well, quickly acclimating with teams or doing the build out by myself.

VOX MEDIA Washington DC Lead Designer

At Vox I had the pleasure of working on an incredibly talented product team. Being with Vox through a period of rapid growth provided a rich educational experience, that I appreciate greatly. I worked primarily as a visual and UI designer, within a rails environment. I was responsible for communication with developers, designers, frontend devs, product owners, advertising etc.

VOX MEDIA

AOL Dulles, VA

Designer

2009-2010

At Aol, I primarily designed for fanhouse.com, which was a top five editorially driven sports news site. However, with significant readership and a strong product team. I also helped design mmafighting.com, which ironically Vox Media wound up acquiring from Aol, while I was at Vox.

Aol.

AOL Dulles, VA

Design Intern

2007-2009

This was my first professional web experience. I was responsible for working with a team, taking creative direction, working towards product launches against tricky deadlines. During my internship I became accustomed with a professional design atmosphere and also learned a great deal from some gifted designers.

AOL.

## Education

Corcoran College of Art & Design WASHINGTON, DC

Tallin University
TALLIN, ESTONIA

## Skills

print design

VISUAL DESIGN FRONT END

complex interface design html5/SCSS

typography fanatic responsive / mobile

editorial design principles Javascript

Skilled with the Adobe familiar w/ js

Creative Suite frameworks(angular, ember)

MISCELLANEOUS
Comfortable with Ruby on
Rails environments
MVC in general
git, version control
node.is

remote work